RINRIN (20)
HOSTESS
SARA (26)
NAIL ARTIST
AYACHERU (24)
HOSTESS
Mmm.
KAZUMA (26)
PART-TIMER
RYOPI (29)
BAR OWNER
TAI-CHAN (22)
HAIRSTYLIST
- They're mad.
- So mad.
Those girls are super pissed.
Yep, and they're just getting started.
So, us girls have something to say.
We want to know if you're serious.
And we mean all of you.
We're seriously wondering why you're here.
MARU (28)
HOST/PRESIDENT
Nothing like the look on men's
faces when women are confronting them.
- That's right.
- So true.
And especially you, Maru.
We wonder
if you're really here to find love.
You haven't stepped up.
Mmm, okay.
What are you doing here?
I know it's only the third day,
and we haven't talked that much,
but so far, it's the girls
who've been making all the moves,
and we wonder if you guys are serious.
We really wonder
what you're thinking about.
Mmm-hmm.
- Why are you here?
- To find love.
That's the thing I'm really missing.
I'm not here for a quick fix.
It's been ten years.
I'm here
because I want to find love again.
So maybe I was slow
when it came to talking
with you all one-on-one.
I know I was.
Well, we want you guys to step it up
and start to get more serious.
We're really putting ourselves out there
with you guys,
and it feels like
you're just not into this.
It feels weak.
- Is that it?
- Mmm.
Okay.
That said,
we have a suggestion for you guys.
We want the guys to make dinner
for all of the girls tonight.
Wait, for real?
- Guys' meal?
- You got it.
- Are you for real?
- Tomorrow, we'll make dinner.
- Mmm-hmm.
Not like we have to exchange favors,
but we think
it'll be good to try this out.
- What do you think?
- We want to see if you can step it up.
- We got it.
- Let's do it.
So, yes?
- Please do.
- Can you cook?
- Not even a little bit.
I'm totally useless.
- Have you even been in a kitchen?
- No way!
No, it's true. I can't make anything.
But if you can cook, it'll be amazing.
- True.
- Yeah.
- Just do your best.
- We will.
And have fun in there.
- Okay, thank you.
- See ya.
- Bye.
- We'll see you girls at dinner.
- See you.
It's looks like they all got in trouble,
and their mom is telling them,
"Get it together."
- Tai-chan's been in trouble before.
- Certainly has.
- Right, he flunked out.
- He flunked.
So this guy's been in more trouble before.
- Oh, a lot more.
- Much more.
Now I get it.
- What should we make?
- I've never done this.
Teppanyaki or yakiniku?
That works. Then we just grill.
Well, I knew
I couldn't keep going on like this.
Mmm.
I don't know, I think they're right
that I'm not taking initiative.
That's true.
Some of it is about my career,
but I've always talked to girls
who talk to me first.
I know I really need to just think clearly
about why I'm here.
And then really go after that. Mmm.
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
RUGGED APPRENTICE TATTOO ARTIST
DRAWN TO TATTOOS' SEX APPEAL
KAZUMA
KABUKICHO HOST BOSS
WHO WANTS TO GET SERIOUS ABOUT LOVE
MARU
IBARAKI HOSTESS WITH A BIKE CREW
LOOKING FOR A HUSBAND
AYACHERU
GYARU HOSTESS FROM MIYAGI
A TSUNDERE WHO HATES TO LOSE
RINRIN
KITASHINCHI BAR OWNER
WHO'S ALL ABOUT THE VIBES
RYOPI
WILD OKINAWAN NAIL ARTIST
WITH A PHOENIX ON HER BACK
SARA
FUKUSHIMA HOSTESS
WHO CHARGES INTO LOVE HEAD-FIRST
SHARAN
FACE-TATTOOED STYLIST WHO LOVES HARD
TAI-CHAN
EDOGAWA RAPPER
SEEKING LOVE WITH HONOR
RUNE
TRUE SELVES LAID BARE
BRING ON LOVE
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON THE LOVE
LOVE DINER
We have to make enough
for ten people, right?
I'll just make hamburgers.
- Sounds good.
- Okay.
- You can eat lettuce, right?
- Mmm.
I'll make lettuce fried rice.
Do you know how to mince? Vegetables?
Do you know what that is?
- See how it's round?
- Mmm.
Start from the edge
and then chop it really fine.
All right.
- Just cut tiny pieces.
- Yeah, okay.
Tai-chan, what are you making?
I'm thinking of taking the beef
and also some of this
to make, like, a fancy meat dish.
That's quite the technique.
It's terrifying. Take off your sunglasses!
I'm so worried for him.
- Can I use all of this?
- Oh, I don't know.
- All of it might be a bit much.
- Yeah, too much.
Ugh.
For tonjiru, I should put in
a lot of ingredients, right?
- Yeah, tonjiru should have a lot.
- It's hearty, right?
We don't talk when cooking, huh?
Women are good with their hands.
- True.
- That's good work.
Yo, how long does it take to cook daikon?
- Those chunks are huge.
- They're so big.
Looks like a choking hazard.
Something's wrong.
Something is very wrong.
How have you only cooked half of it?
Why is this happening?
Whoa, Maru's kind of
making something super intense.
This might be terrible, for real.
I can't serve this, it's so bad.
You can.
- It's the thought.
- Mmm.
- It's the thought that counts.
- We're cooking from our hearts.
What is that stuff?
It's a hamburger
that was cooked and fell apart.
- That's meat?
- Yes.
You can't even tell anymore.
Have they been cooking for two hours?
- Yeah, right?
- That's crazy.
But they're putting in an effort.
- I guess.
- Curious to know what they make?
- What do you think they're making?
- What if it's super fancy?
- What if it is?
- No.
- They're looking up online recipes, right?
- I think they are.
- They're not doing anything.
- Yeah. Seriously.
- They're lounging. Hanging out.
- They're just sitting.
Boil it for… eight minutes? Shoot.
- He's good.
- Looks good.
- Right?
- It's looking right.
- Because he's a bartender.
- Right.
We should be cooking on low heat.
Low heat, right. For it to simmer.
If it's on too high,
then the surface will get all burnt.
- Mmm.
- That's probably good.
- Huge pieces.
- Those are gigantic bites.
- It looks good. Right?
- It does. Yeah.
- Tai-chan, you're done?
- Yeah, I'm done.
This should be ready. Let's go.
Hey.
Oh, sure, come in.
Okay.
Your dinner has been served, ladies.
- It's a guys' meal.
- Okay.
- After you, ladies.
- Yay!
- We're ready.
- Let's do it!
- We've been waiting.
- Make your way to the living room.
- I'm excited.
- This is awesome.
They're tired.
- You're right.
- Everyone's exhausted.
Okay.
- Wow.
- Please, come.
- After you.
- Oh, me? Thanks.
- What?
- Okay.
- Oh, wow. What's this?
- Thank you.
- This is legit. Insane.
- Oh, wow.
- So amazing.
- Okay, fried rice?
- Fried rice?
- Fried rice, hamburgers…
- It's beef.
- Beef?
- That's amazing!
- Oh, but it looks kind of…
- It looks delicious!
- It's a guys' meal!
- This is great!
- What's this?
This reaction is amazing.
For real, this is the best.
- Oh, you were saying you wanted tonjiru!
- I was!
- What? You're lying.
- That's amazing!
- What?
- That's wild!
Yeah, I've been saying that
since I got here.
- How crazy is that?
- So wild.
Oh. Nice timing.
The guys tried to do something new,
working hard to make a nice dinner.
Alcohol is allowed today.
- Yeah!
- Thank God! We did it!
Oh! So sometimes they can drink,
and sometimes they can't?
- Yes, that's right.
- Oh. Okay, I've got it.
Because people tend to misbehave
when they drink.
- Sometimes they become rule breakers.
- Okay, okay.
- Time to drink!
- All right!
- Wanna do the honors?
- Should I toast?
- Yeah. You do it.
- Uh, let's do this thing!
Cheers!
- Let's eat!
- So fun!
- I love when we can drink.
- Yeah!
Tasty.
- Ah, wow!
- This slaps.
I'm all up in my feelings now.
- That hit hard.
- I'm really gonna cry.
Okay, dig in.
- Let's eat!
- Enjoy.
- Who made hamburgers?
- Maru outdid himself.
- Maru made them.
- Maru, right?
- Be honest, I want to know.
- I bet.
What… What you think.
- It looks like you made it.
- It looks cooked.
Really?
- Mmm.
- But how does it taste?
Mmm, it's good.
- Getting burgers right isn't easy.
- Good!
Oh, that's excellent.
He must feel great now.
- Rinrin.
- Maru, great job.
Look at him.
Seriously, I'm so happy.
This hamburger is good, Maru.
- It's good?
- It is.
Oh, I'm so happy.
- What's your trick to getting it so juicy?
- Why's it so good?
- I always believed in you.
- Ah, thanks.
- Good, that's great.
- It's seriously good.
Delicious.
- The tonjiru is definitely…
- Tonjiru is comfort food.
I won't judge how the vegetables are cut.
- Oh, okay.
- Are there carrots?
- The carrots are--
- So easy to tell.
I was gonna put carrots in there,
but I don't really like them.
- I decided to leave them out.
- It's Kazuma-style.
- It was good. Thank you.
- It's good.
- Really.
- That's a great smile.
Who made the fried rice?
That's the one I can't tell.
- Yeah.
- It's amazing.
Mmm?
- Mmm? Who made it?
- Mmm.
- Who?
- I did.
- What?
- Seriously?
- I made the rice.
- For real?
- Seriously?
I want more of it.
- Oh, God.
- Yum!
Oh, wow.
- So, this is what cooking's like?
- Mmm.
Well, cheers.
- Nice. Maru is smiling too.
- He cracked a smile.
- Yay!
- This is fierce.
- Taste good?
- Mmm.
I can't believe it.
- This is so nice.
- This made me so happy.
Amazing!
Honestly, I want to thank you
for giving us a chance to do all of this.
- Yeah.
- I'm grateful.
But that's the thing, it makes me happy
that you guys
all worked together to do this
because, uh…
The thing is…
Mmm.
…I seriously worked, like, so hard.
So hard, right?
Well, I'm really moved.
Seriously, thank you.
Taka from ONE OK ROCK is joining us.
Thank you. You think this is funny?
- We appreciate it.
- Hysterical.
I can't get over the fact
you're watching this with us.
- It's great.
- Did you watch Season 1?
- Oh, yeah, I watched all of it.
- What?
- Yeah, and then I sent her a message.
- He did.
I thought it was such a cool new approach
to entertainment.
- Oh, that's amazing.
- It meant so much.
You know, Taka is an urban rich yankii.
Huh? I'm not familiar with that term--
- What does that mean?
- Yeah, forgive me.
- That's a new shampoo, right?
- It's not a shampoo.
And, no, it's not the latest
hair treatment on the market.
- No?
- Actually, it's urban luxury yankii.
- That's amazing.
- That's who Taka is.
- I'd say Taka is the big-brother type.
- Thank you.
Someone who looks out
for the younger generation.
- Oh, I see.
- He's a really excellent mentor.
So, for this show, I wanted his insight
as that honorary big brother,
to give his perspective
- on the yankii participants here.
- So flattered.
He came back and said,
"Megumi, for you, of course, I'll do it."
- So we have some urban rich yankii.
- He's an urban rich yankii.
When it comes to this,
I have to respect my elders.
- Oh, how commendable.
- Yes.
So that's how you see Megumi.
- No, he's right.
- She's like a big sister.
- She's a boss lady. Thank you, Boss.
- Oh, yeah.
Well, what are your thoughts
about this versus Season1?
Well, you know, I actually…
I actually do think that
the energy of the Season 2 participants
might be more intense here
- than with the participants of Season 1.
- I see.
- That's very insightful.
- Oh, is it?
I think you're right.
Well, this cast has seen the show,
so they have a good understanding
of the premise and how it all works.
Watching the new cast navigate the show
with all of that information,
I think it gives this season
another level, you know?
- Yes.
- I find that super interesting.
So I'm paying attention to that
as I watch.
Thank you.
You sound like you should be a producer.
- My apologies.
- Very astute. You're right.
That's truly what's happening.
With Season 1, we didn't know
what was going on, neither did the cast.
But with Season 2, they're participating
with more of an understanding.
- So they're more invested.
- Yes.
As Taka said,
there's nothing like the face of a man
- when he's being confronted by a woman.
- Oh, totally.
I think once men hit elementary school,
or even kindergarten,
that's the face they make for life.
That face right there.
- Confusion.
- Completely bewildered.
Yeah.
This is what a stunned man looks like.
I'm sure you two have been confronted
by your mothers or girlfriends before,
so when this is happening,
when you're making this face,
what's going through your mind?
Mmm.
First of all, I never know
why I'm being yelled at.
- That's mostly what you're thinking.
- Yeah, that's mostly it.
So, while the yelling is happening,
I'm slowly figuring out
why I'm in trouble.
And then, it dawns on me,
"Oh, okay, that's why."
These are processing faces, right?
- That's right.
- "Why am I being yelled at?"
It's the face of trying
to remember what you did.
But, still, when you see him
in there mincing onions,
he seems so precious.
- He wasn't mincing, he was shredding them.
- Oh, so he was shredding onions.
- He's a carpenter.
- He's destroying them.
- He's shaving them.
- Yeah.
And you really like to cook lots of meals
for your friends, don't you, Taka?
- Yes. Yes, I do.
- Wow! That's so amazing.
- You also cook for big groups, right?
- Yeah, I love to cook.
In my work,
I'm always performing in front of people,
so I'm always trying to
take care of them, I would say.
I think I am more comfortable
being the one who takes care of people,
even in my private life, yeah.
So you're a giver.
- Comes to you naturally.
- That's true.
And, you know, that's why
he's an urban luxury yankii.
Oh! That's how it comes together.
- A mentor, but…
- The yankii part is barely there.
- I know, right?
- Urban and luxury.
Urban and luxury part is too strong.
We might not need the yankii part.
- Being in the ocean was fun.
- So fun.
- We were out there a long time.
- Yeah.
So this is after they went scuba diving.
- A café. Mmm.
- Yeah. This is so insane.
It's really nice. Cheers.
- Cheers. Thank you.
- Thanks.
- This is delicious.
- Yeah, it's good.
Okay.
So they're gonna swap drinks
like that, okay.
- Mmm.
- Mmm-hmm.
- It's good.
- Good. They're similar.
- Oh, sorry.
- Oops, sorry.
- I'm dying. That's so funny.
- All mango.
Oh, my God.
Oh, wait, pancakes!
- Your chocolate pancake.
- Thank you.
Caramel pancake.
- I want chocolate.
- Sure. You can eat it.
- Oh, let's try both.
- I wanna try both.
- Whoa!
- It's super good, right?
Feed it to me. Try.
Yeah?
- Feed me.
- Want me to feed you?
Yeah. It's like tamagoyaki.
It's not like tamagoyaki.
- It's yellow too.
- Here.
Oh, wow--
What the hell?
All the caramel was dripping.
Thanks.
This is intense. With this view
and these carbs and everything.
They must be overstimulated.
- I know, right?
- I'd be so overwhelmed.
So, Sharan, I have to say,
at first, it always seemed like
you were focused on Tai-chan.
- That's what it felt like to me.
- Mmm.
Yeah, and then,
you did the race with him, and you won.
So why did you choose me
to go on a date with
instead of Tai-chan?
- I was gonna choose Tai-chan.
- Oh, yeah?
But then, it was like, you know, he…
Um, he just isn't… he isn't really funny.
- Wow!
- Come on.
That's the most hurtful thing you can say.
I know, to be told that you're not funny.
Do you know what I mean?
Oh, in your opinion, right?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- So…
- So being funny is important to you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The thing is, um, if someone doesn't
make me laugh, it's sort of a red flag.
Mmm, mmm.
So I was like,
"Maybe I'll go on this date
with you, then."
Because we have similar interests,
and you laugh all of the time.
- Oh, my God. All the time?
- We are-- We are similar, right?
- I get it.
- Yeah, so…
If we're laughing together,
then, okay, let's hang out.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
- So he's her type, then.
- How was it then, today?
Did your impression change, then?
You're so easy to talk to.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Do you think I'm funny?
- Yeah, and fun to be with.
- Today's been really great.
- Yeah?
- Mmm.
- That's great.
I do wanna hang out again.
- Again?
- Mmm.
Yeah.
- Let's talk.
- Mmm.
- Okay.
Thanks for this.
- You too.
- Yeah.
Let's talk again.
- Thank you.
- Wow, okay, a hug.
- Looks they had a lot of fun.
What was that?
Yo, dude. They're finally back.
- Hey, I'm back.
- He's arrived.
- What took you so long?
- Why're you getting in so late?
I'm seriously tired. Let me sit for a sec.
I'm back.
Today was…
So, first thing,
I got to ride on the back of her bike.
Mmm.
After that,
then we got to go out scuba diving.
- Whoa.
- Scuba diving?
- The kind where you go underwater.
- Oh.
- How was it? Good?
- I want a shower.
Yeah, it was super fun.
- You had a date the first day.
- The sauna, yeah.
Which one did you like better?
Which one? Mmm…
Well, for me, I think,
you know, uh…
the sauna was…
the sauna was my first experience,
and also, because Sara was the one
that I was interested in from the start.
Yeah, so, yeah, I would say
my experience with Sara was great.
As far as romantic feelings go--
Did your first impression
of Sharan change?
- Yeah, I'm curious.
- You weren't with your partner.
Because at the beginning,
you started out liking Sara,
and then, you were with Sharan all day.
- Did your impression change at all?
- Did it?
My impression… I don't know, like,
when you're on a date
in that sort of setting, like that,
I think your feelings can…
Well, it makes sense that
they can waiver a little.
- Toward Sharan?
- Yeah.
- Though you went to the sauna with Sara?
- Though you took my spot?
- Even though you wanted to go.
- Right.
- This dude, seriously.
- Are you saying Sharan's better than Sara?
- No, not better than.
- Wow!
- But seriously, though…
You're obsessed.
It's a weird position
because I was chosen to go on the date.
- I see your point.
- You know? She asked me.
Hey, what do you think
after hearing about this now?
Honestly, I'm still wondering
why she didn't choose me.
- I would too.
- Like, damn, it should've been me.
If I hadn't won the race,
she wouldn't have gone on the date.
- Right, I know.
- That's fair, I think.
But I think it'd be better
if he could wait a bit, right?
- I'm gonna--
- But we're all dealing with it.
- Are you cool if I talk to her?
- You're asking me? Mmm.
- I want to know what she's thinking.
- Totally fair.
- Yeah, I understand.
- You should.
- I want to hear her tell me.
- Tai-chan got a bum deal today.
- Sure.
- Yeah, you should ask her.
- I'll ask her.
- Ask who?
- Sharan.
- Good luck.
- If she says what she said earlier, he's--
- Yeah, he's gonna cry.
- He won't be able to go on.
- He can't take it.
I think that would make him
drop out of school immediately, right?
- He won't come back from that.
- He won't.
- Hey, welcome back!
- I'm back. Okay.
- Sit down.
- I'm so tired.
- We want to hear about it.
- We have questions.
How was it?
Oh, it was insane.
So, did your feelings change?
- Well--
- You still like Tai-chan?
I think it's 50-50 now.
- What?
- Really?
Yeah, because--
Wait, everyone was probably so surprised
when I picked him, right?
- We totally were.
- Yeah, we were shocked.
- Everyone was.
- Everyone was. Tai-chan was about to cry.
- He was.
- Really?
The thing is,
I don't think he's that funny.
She said it again.
She's gonna say it to his face.
Tai-chan, right? Yeah, you said that.
- Yeah.
- Did something happen with Rune?
- Well…
- Okay.
- It's not like there's…
- Something happened.
- Wait.
- Some connection.
Judging by your face, there was.
At the end, we talked,
did a fist bump, a squeeze, then--
- Yeah?
- It was… How can I say it?
You had a squeeze?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Wow.
- That's it then.
- And then you said goodbye?
Yeah, I said
it was really easy to talk to him.
- Mmm.
- That's nice.
So I was thinking
I should talk to Tai-chan now,
to apologize
for confusing him today, I mean.
You should talk to him.
Talk to him while he's smoking.
Yeah, Tai-chan is--
Right.
- Hey.
- Hey!
That's so weird.
- That's so sick!
- That's so cool!
- What is this?
- We were just talking about you.
- Come, let's talk.
- This is so weird.
- It's really weird.
- It's not weird.
You showed up,
and I was just about to find you.
It's not weird at all.
We were just talking about you.
You're the best, Tai-chan!
- Nice one.
- Thank you.
- Go, Tai-chan!
- I'm gonna borrow her.
Borrow her and go.
- For real.
- Take her for as long as you want.
That was amazing. The timing was perfect.
- That's crazy!
- That was insane, right?
I can't believe
she's said it out loud twice.
- She might say it again.
- A couple times now. Mmm.
CLASSROOM
- How was the date?
- Oh, the date?
- Mmm.
- It was fun.
- But I'm really sorry.
- No, no, it's not like that, I--
I mean it.
No, I'm not mad about anything, really.
If you didn't choose me, then…
Mmm.
That just means…
Well, if you really had feelings for me,
you would've picked me, right?
So I just haven't done enough
to win you over.
But I do want to know why you chose Rune.
Um, well, I…
- Oh, no, you're really too nice.
- Mmm.
How should I put this?
Um, it's like we never really joke around.
- Mmm.
- You know?
- No, I don't.
- How can I say it?
- It's just different with him.
- Mmm.
You're so nice,
and you're kind of a cool guy.
- Mmm, mmm.
- You're serious.
- Too serious?
- Yeah, I like to laugh a lot.
Mmm.
Okay.
I want you to lighten up, I think,
or, like, um…
You were really intense the other day.
Right? You won for me.
But being cool is…
Like, you're always cool, you're cool,
but for me, that's just not enough.
I want real.
Okay, that's pretty straightforward too.
Mmm.
- Rune and I are similar.
- Mmm.
And he's, like, a rapper,
and, you know, we both like hip hop.
- Right?
- Mmm.
I like that. I connect with people
who have the same interests as me.
I wanted to get to know him more,
so that's why I asked him out on a date.
- I see.
- You get it?
- I got it.
- Mmm.
I think I just really want us
to joke around more.
- Sure.
- Yeah.
Sure.
If there's another challenge and the women
get the chance to choose again,
I'll be ready.
And if I win a challenge,
I am gonna ask you out.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- So be ready for it.
Mmm, okay.
Joke around with me more.
- I will.
- Really.
- I'll see you.
- Seriously, I'm sorry.
- Good night.
- Yeah.
- Bye.
- Okay.
Bye-bye.
You know, he's going to be wrecked
if he watches this when it airs.
- I know, he'll be so hurt.
- When this is over.
This show's made by a heartless staff.
You know?
- It was good. I was shocked.
- That's awesome. For real?
- It was hands down delicious.
- Seriously?
Did you know you can't taste
the hamburgers while you're cooking them?
- Mmm.
- I was worried it would taste awful.
- You should be proud.
- I'm so glad. I was relieved.
But seriously, it didn't taste like it was
made by someone who has never cooked.
Mmm.
- So, like, to be straight with you, I'm…
- Mmm.
I'm definitely into you,
and I'm not really interested
in anyone else here, right now, at all.
So I'm telling everyone, straight up,
that if I had to choose someone right now,
I'd probably, you know, like, go for Maru,
and it's not like I don't want to keep
talking to the other guys, because I do,
but if there was like a date?
- Like, who would I want to go with?
- Mmm-hmm.
I'd definitely say
I'd want to go with you, Maru.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
- To be straight with you right back…
- Mmm.
…um, I think you're by far
the most outstanding girl that's here.
I like that.
Yeah, well, I did get a letter
from Ayacheru, and I didn't send her one.
Of course it felt good to receive a letter
and to know she was interested in me.
It was clear from the start
that we really got along,
and I definitely thought she was cool too.
But, you know,
I really felt like I was just being
the same old me in there with her.
The guys said that to me just now.
Like, I was acting like a host, I guess.
And then I thought, "Am I? Maybe I am."
I wanted…
I wanted to talk to her, but now I wonder,
where does that feeling come from?
That's really hard to think about.
What I've been doing as a host
is different from actual love.
- Because when you're a host…
- Mmm.
…you work
in a totally different environment
than where they are now.
So I'm sure,
when it comes to finding love,
they're probably not used to what
it feels like to have honest feelings.
This setup might be confusing for them.
Ironically, they might be
the least experienced in love.
- That's true.
- Mmm.
- Being a host must be a tough job.
- It's so true, yeah.
Rinrin.
GUYS
- Hey.
Can we cuddle?
- Wait, what?
- I said, can we cuddle?
- What's going on?
- Isn't she cute?
- Are you shy?
- Shut up.
Cheers.
So, am I still the one
that you're interested in?
- Mmm-hmm. You're the top choice.
- Always?
- Mmm.
- Hey-o. Hey-o.
- You have a good taste in men.
- Shut up. Don't joke.
Shut up.
I didn't know you were so girly.
- What? Oh, God!
- Oh, my.
So, here's the thing, okay?
No, listen to me, listen, okay?
When it comes to someone I like
or a potential boyfriend,
I just really like to cuddle up
when I'm drunk.
What are you, like, a puppy?
- Mmm?
- Are you a puppy?
Mmm-hmm.
You are so innocent.
I just want to sleep like this.
That is not what I expected.
The difference between this
and how you normally act is huge.
- Am I cute?
- Mmm-hmm.
I love cooking.
- That's good.
- Mmm.
You win a man's heart through his stomach?
Mmm-hmm, I do.
- Oh, my.
- Wow.
That's nice.
- That's a love grip.
- Is that a "love grip"?
- Definitely a love grip.
- I see, that's what it looks like.
This is amazing!
They're totally getting together.
It's been a while
since I did this with someone.
Aw.
- I think I like you the most now.
- Now?
- Mmm-hmm.
- And what about tomorrow?
I don't know. It's up to you.
- No one else here is funny at all.
- Nah.
- No one's funny.
- You never know, maybe Kazuma.
Oh, yeah? You go for it.
Okay, come here, you.
Come on.
We're serious, then.
What?
Ah!
Oh, what's going on?
I'm embarrassed.
What do you mean "embarrassed"?
You're a tsundere.
God, is she blushing?
This is amazing.
I did not think you were such a good girl.
- She's cute.
- That looks fun.
- Okay, so there's a development.
- Wow.
- Looks like they're pretty serious now.
- Rinrin and Ryopi are moving forward.
- This is amazing.
- They kissed each other.
- Like were watching a movie.
- Look at that angle.
She usually behaves like such a tough girl
when she's with the group.
- What do you think about this side of her?
- Guys would love seeing this side.
Because most men
totally fall for this kind of thing.
- Of course.
- Yeah. Just look at that innocent smile.
- Look at these innocent faces.
- They smile from the heart.
- Yes!
- They're not actors, right?
- They're real people.
- Real people. Normal people.
- Ordinary people, right?
- Everyday people.
- They're all so expressive.
- They are.
Sharan's eyes are kind of heart-shaped.
- She's so expressive.
- Yes.
She looks like
she's been on camera before.
She does.
I think most people
would've gone for Tai-chan there.
- Yeah.
- But I feel like
maybe she chose someone else deliberately
to hurt Tai-chan or something.
- Oh, yeah?
- Ah!
Because Rune is probably the most
glamorous guy in the whole school, right?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
The fact that she chose him
right away for her date
makes me think she might be playing games.
- Mmm.
- Oh!
I definitely feel that from her.
Like, she's working on a different level
than everyone else.
Do you think so?
When he asked, "Why did you choose me?"
she was like, "We both laugh very easily."
- That's shady, to say "easily," I think.
- Right, I get it.
- That's not saying much, yeah.
- Right.
- Rune is also pretty reserved so far.
- Oh. Mmm.
- I feel we haven't seen the real him.
- I can't get a read on Rune yet.
True.
But Tai-chan is really great because…
he said, "Be ready, I'm going to ask you
out on a date next time."
- That didn't happen in Part 1, right?
- Oh, no. Not at all, no.
Oh, it didn't?
Passive might not be
the best way to put it,
but Tai-chan wasn't like this.
- "Tai-chan wasn't like this," okay.
- No, he was not like this.
- We're happy because we've been watching.
- It's really great to see.
And this is the first time
he's expressed his feelings clearly.
- This pose is so cool.
- His finger's so straight.
How does he stretch it out like that?
Badly In Love is a program
that helps people straighten out.
- That's right.
- It's been like this for all of Season 2.
- Yes, we even teach them ethics.
- That's amazing.
Some episodes are 90% ethics.
Right.
Like, "What am I even watching?"
Let's do it.
Thank you.
- I got you.
- Thank you.
It's crazy, your hair is so thick.
- Okay, is it really?
- Mmm.
It doesn't look like you'll ever go bald.
- Guys with my hair don't ever go bald?
- No.
Tai-chan is a hairstylist.
- That focus is a good look on him.
- He looks confident.
- When he's working, yeah.
- He's cool.
Mmm.
Okay, you're all done.
- Can I see?
- Mmm.
I really like the friendship vibe
developing here between these guys.
It's not completely smooth here.
- It looks good.
- Really?
Mmm.
Can I take this back?
Uh, so,
I wanted to talk to you
about the first day.
Oh? Okay.
When I threw the chalkboard eraser at you.
Oh.
It's only been a week
since I got here, you know,
but it's been
such a crazy and intense week.
Oh.
I realize that if someone had done that
to me, I'd be pissed.
I wasn't thinking about
how you might have felt that day.
- I get it, yeah.
- Yeah.
So I wanted to officially apologize
for all of that.
Mmm.
You were the one who came to me
to apologize for it.
- Oh.
- I thought that was very…
very mature of you, you know?
So, yeah,
I acted pretty childish that day.
I've really learned a lot
from living with everyone so far.
Mmm.
- So, I'm sorry.
- Aw!
- That's nice.
- Okay. Honestly, I was just sad.
Mmm, yeah, I bet.
We wrote those messages the day
before graduation, and they were erased.
I understand how that graduation
didn't mean anything to you guys,
so I get why you did what you did.
Honestly, I wasn't even that angry
because I really was
just super sad, you know?
- Mmm.
- Oh, of course, yeah.
- But I feel much better now.
- Mmm.
- We're good. Let's just move on, okay?
We're okay.
Okay. I'm sorry.
- No, I'm sorry.
- Nah.
- We're good.
- Okay.
- Tai-chan.
- I love that.
- He's grown.
- Men who apologize are cool.
You're right. That was cool of Kazuma.
- You have slot machines?
- We do.
- That's so cool.
- We have it all.
Aw, it looks so fun.
- It is fun.
- Yeah.
Mostly, it is.
Okay, so,
I have to ask you a question then.
So you hugged Sharan yesterday, right?
- Oh, man.
- Wait…
I did.
I was wondering why
you didn't tell me that.
- Why?
- Mmm.
- It wasn't a big deal.
- It's what I did with Ms. Higa.
- What do you mean?
Saying thank you.
- Oh.
- We fist-bumped and then, like…
- So…
- It wasn't like we were
having a long and passionate hug
or anything.
Oh, sure, that's a believable excuse.
Yeah, that's definitely the face of a guy
who lies to his girlfriend on the regular.
He looks like a guy
who's staring into space for help.
He's totally zoned out.
The face of a man
looking to the stars for a lifeline.
It was a quick hug
and a fist bump, that's it.
Mmm.
Well, that's what
I've been worried about.
- I'd say. Seriously.
- No, no, don't worry about it.
Why not? You went on a date.
Well, yeah,
but it's not like I asked her out.
- I was invited, and then I went.
- Mmm.
Well, that's the thing
I wanted to talk to you about. Mmm.
But I didn't go on the date because
I was interested in her or anything.
- Mmm.
- That's good then.
Thank you.
- Yikes. I don't like this vibe at all.
- I'm nervous.
- It's scary.
- It is.
So, I said to him,
"You went on a date with Sharan,
and then…
she said that you gave her a squeeze?"
- Mmm.
- Oh. Mmm?
- Did you say that?
- I said that.
Then what?
And so when I said that…
Oh, no, no, no.
…he said, "It was like a thank you,
a fist bump, and just a hug."
Mmm.
And I said, "Okay, that's what happened."
He said "just a hug"?
So annoying.
Annoying? What's annoying?
Rune is.
- Rune is annoying?
- How come?
- Why?
- Because he said that to you.
He said it was "just a hug."
'Cause he said the word "just," right?
That's what's bothering you?
"It wasn't a big deal" kind of thing.
He was like,
"We were just hugging as friends."
"It's not like
I was trying anything with her."
- He said that.
- Mmm.
So it's not like
I don't understand what he said.
It's more like,
why would he even do any of that?
I just really wanted to know
how Rune felt,
so I decided to ask him
straight up about it.
- Mmm.
- He didn't try to hide anything.
- He's not like that.
- It's just… not cool.
I'm not annoyed by you, but, um, like--
I'm not even annoyed,
but it's the way he put it.
Mmm. Mmm.
So, if he says, "It was just that,"
then he shouldn't have given her
a squeeze in the first place.
- Mmm.
- Who wants that?
Yeah, I understand that.
A hug is different from a squeeze?
I told Sara that it was a squeeze.
And then, she asked Rune,
and he said, "We just hugged."
And I thought
the way he said it was irritating.
For the first time, I thought,
"This is so annoying."
It just really bothered me.
Oh, no, no, no.
- I think I'm… I'm over Rune.
- What?
And I feel like
I've already found someone else I like.
That was fast.
Tai-chan.
- What?
- Huh?
I really like Tai-chan, yeah.
I'm into him.
I feel like I get along
with Tai-chan better, actually.
Rune is too serious for me.
I feel like it's clear that
we're just too different.
- Huh?
- But you said you were the same.
- That you both laughed at the same things.
- Yeah, right?
- Wow, that's crazy.
- Didn't she say Tai-chan wasn't funny?
She definitely did.
In fact, she said it twice.
Okay, I think the mind games
have started here a little bit.
Everyone,
please gather together in the classroom
because, today,
a new female transfer student
will be joining you.
- Ooh!
- Oh!
- It's a woman.
- Here we go.
- We have a transfer student?
- Yes.
Let's go.
- It's a woman.
- Mmm.
- Send her home.
- We really don't need her.
It would've better if it was a man.
Should the girls sit in the front?
When it's a guy,
we'll sit in the front. If he comes.
Bring it on.
Ten people?
What? So rude of you.
I'm nostalgic.
- Are you freaked out?
- Hmm?
- You heard me. You're freaked out?
- Should we go already?
- Hmm?
- What?
- You're so bad.
- Let's go then.
- I'm gonna go, "Hey, sit down here."
- That's nice.
- Good, right?
Everyone is always so nervous
before the new student comes.
It's fun, right?
BADLY IN LOVE MARINE ACADEMY
Hurry up and come, bitch.
Bitch?
Bitch, okay.
Your clapbacks are getting good.
- Whoa! Who is this?
- Wait a minute.
- What?! Where did this girl come from?
- Out of nowhere.
- We have a different vibe!
- She's very different!
This whole thing
will be hilarious after it's over.
- She's here.
- She's here?
What?
Damn, lady.
Damn.
So nice to meet you.
My name is Mimina Ito.
- Yeah!
- She's totally different.
- Why are you screaming?
- Woo-hoo!
- Wait, she's so different.
- Now it's getting interesting!
I love it!
- What do you love?
- The action is starting!
Well, I work in Osaka
as a bar hostess in Kitashinchi.
- Oh!
- Come on, girls. Hang in there.
This is the best possible curveball.
Um, my nickname is Mimi,
and I'm very happy to be here. So hello.
- Hello. Good to see you.
- Nice to meet you.
MIMINA ITO, MIMI (29)
I work as a hostess
in a bar in Kitashinchi.
I was consistently the number-one girl
for a little over a year there.
And, yes,
I've been the face of the club ever since.
My father is probably a yakuza.
He has the right tattoos.
I've been beaten up by him a lot.
The police were called.
They got involved a few times, yeah.
I wasn't getting along with my stepfather.
There was no place
I was comfortable calling my home.
So I was thrown into a children's home.
I was always fighting.
I don't usually pick fights, though.
But if someone pushes me, I'll fight back.
- Wow.
- This is so wild right now.
- This is gonna be bad.
- So sick.
- It's feeling dangerous.
- She's not gonna mix with them.
- It's been a while.
- How are you?
- What?
- He's a familiar face.
- They know each other?
- I'm used to serving her like a slave.
- No, no, no.
- Uh-oh.
- That's not good.
- Just go home.
- I'm not going home.
- You should. We don't need you here.
- I just got here. No.
Do you want love?
- Mmm… Yeah, I think so.
- Why are you here?
Why? To fall in love.
No, you're not.
- Uh, yeah, I am.
- Don't lie to me.
- I'm not lying.
- What?
- We don't need you. Go home.
- You go home.
- No.
- Why should I?
- Get the hell out.
- Shut up, ugly.
- Get out. You're the ugly one.
- You're out of control.
- Get out.
- So lame.
- Who is? Don't mess with me.
All right.
- I'm sorry for putting you through that.
- I'm gonna make it.
- I'm so sorry.
- I know.
It happened fast.
But my face looked
just like those guys, right?
- You looked like Tai-chan.
- Exactly like him, right?
- Wow, the best possible plot twist.
- Yeah.
I love it.